Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/wolfgang-seibold-629b68a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

SpaceClaim

C++

C#

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)
German (Native or Bilingual)

Wolfgang Seibold

Senior Principal Software Engineer at ANSYS, Inc.

Lafayette, Colorado, United States

Summary

I'm a software developer with broad knowledge and experience in solving geometry problems. I have a strong background in mathematics and computer science, which I apply in developing novel solutions for various clients in the field of additive manufacturing, topology optimization and geometric modeling.

Experience

Ansys

9 years 7 months

Senior Principal Software Engineer October 2020 - Present (3 years 2 months)

Boulder

Working as part and managing the geometry team at Ansys, focusing on the confluence of polygonal, volumetric, traditional CAD forms and subdivision surfaces.

Principal Software Engineer May 2014 - October 2022 (8 years 6 months) Boulder

SpaceClaim

Senior Geometry Developer October 2010 - May 2014 (3 years 8 months)

Spatial Corp
Principle Software Engineer
January 2001 - September 2010 (9 years 9 months)

Education

University of Otago
PhD, Computer Science · (1996 - 2000)

Paris Lodron Universität Salzburg Leibeserziehung · (1993 - 1995)

Johannes Kepler Universität Linz Diplom Ingenieur, Technische Mathematik · (1990 - 1995)